
 [
      {
        "question": "The one universal spirit or creator in Hinduism",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "hinduism",
        "choice3": "siddhartha",
        "choice4": "eightful path",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "One of the world's oldest religions and is the 3rd largest",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "hinduism",
        "choice3": "siddhartha",
        "choice4": "eightful path",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Who founded Buddhism",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "hinduism",
        "choice3": "siddhartha",
        "choice4": "eightful path",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "Rules that you should follow for living right",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "hinduism",
        "choice3": "siddhartha",
        "choice4": "eightful path",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "Buddha believed that people can find spiritual truth or enlightment and end their suffering if they stopped",
        "choice1": "selfish desires",
        "choice2": "The Thervada and Mahayana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "hinduism",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What were the two groups of Buddists who spread the Buddhas ideas southeast Asia.",
        "choice1": "selfish desires",
        "choice2": "The Thervada and Mahayana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "hinduism",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "Besides Buddhism and Hinduism, what is the other Indian faith that developed ",
        "choice1": "selfish desires",
        "choice2": "The Thervada and Mahayana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "hinduism",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "A major religion that developed in Ancient India",
        "choice1": "selfish desires",
        "choice2": "The Thervada and Mahayana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "hinduism",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "The universal spirit worshiped by Hindus",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "reincarnation",
        "choice3": "dharma",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "The rebirth of the soul",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "reincarnation",
        "choice3": "dharma",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "A persons personal duty, based on the individuals place in society",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "reincarnation",
        "choice3": "dharma",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "A force that is created by a persons actions, it determines whether a persons soul will be reborn into a higher or lower form of life",
        "choice1": "brahman",
        "choice2": "reincarnation",
        "choice3": "dharma",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "A religion founded in Ancient India by the religious teacher Buddha",
        "choice1": "Buddhism",
        "choice2": "nervana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "A state of perfect happiness and peace",
        "choice1": "Buddhism",
        "choice2": "nervana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "A religion of Ancient India that does not believe in a supreme being,  enphasizes nonviolent and respect for all living things",
        "choice1": "Buddhism",
        "choice2": "nervana",
        "choice3": "jainism",
        "choice4": "karma",
        "answer": 3
      }
  ]
  